<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipes</string>

    <string name="etc">…</string>

    <string name="recipe_app_name">30 Days Of Recipes</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_01">Easy Salmon Cakes</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_01">These healthy salmon cakes are a delicious way to boost your intake of omega-3s. It is also a great way to use convenient canned (or leftover) salmon.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_01">45 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_01">47 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_02">Zucchini Frittata</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_02">This vegetable-studded frittata recipe is one of the quickest meals you can make. Make it for breakfast, or serve for lunch or dinner with a tossed salad and a slice of olive oil-drizzled crusty baguette.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_02">20 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_02">229 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_03">Zucchini Noodles</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_03">Cut some carbs and use spiralized zucchini in place of noodles in this zesty pesto pasta dish recipe. Top with Cajun-seasoned shrimp to complete this quick and easy dinner.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_03">35 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_03">446 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_04">Greek Chicken</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_04">This Greek-inspired chicken and vegetable sheet-pan meal is bursting with flavor. The chicken is coated in a mayonnaise and bread crumb mixture, roasted alongside asparagus, cremini mushrooms and grape tomatoes and then served with a lemon-feta vinaigrette.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_04">30 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_04">306 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_05">Hummus Sandwich</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_05">This mile-high vegetable and hummus sandwich makes the perfect heart-healthy vegetarian lunch to go. Mix it up with different flavors of hummus and different types of vegetables, depending on your mood.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_05">10 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_05">325 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_06">Egg Sweet Potato Toast</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_06">Skip the gluten and get some vitamin C with this healthy sweet potato toast recipe. Topped with spinach, egg and a dash of hot sauce, it\'s a delicious alternative to eggs Benedict.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_06">10 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_06">124 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_07">Green Smoothie</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_07">The combination of kale and avocado makes this healthy smoothie recipe extra green. Chia seeds lend this creamy smoothie a heart-healthy punch of fiber and omega-3 fatty acids. Source: EatingWell Magazine, March 2019</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_07">5 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_07">343 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_08">Avocado Salad</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_08">Bursting with nutrient-rich produce, this California-inspired salad is a delicious and satisfying way to get your vitamins. We love the unique combination of blueberries, edamame, and goat cheese. Source: Diabetic Living Magazine, Summer 2020</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_08">20 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_08">368 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_09">Mushroom Shawarma</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_09">The bold spices and cooling and creamy tahini-yogurt sauce make these vegetarian pitas a home run for lunch or dinner. The meaty, umami-rich mushrooms do enough heavy lifting so that you don\'t miss the meat at all. Source: EatingWell.com, May 2020</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_09">15 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_09">281 KCAL</string>

    <string name="recipe_title_10">Roasted Eggplant Pasta</string>
    <string name="recipe_description_10">This easy roasted eggplant pasta dish is dressed with eggplant, fresh cherry tomatoes and plenty of fresh herbs. Feta cheese adds a savory note while the balsamic dressing brightens the flavor. It\'s the perfect summer vegetarian dinner.</string>
    <string name="recipe_duration_10">10 MIN</string>
    <string name="recipe_kcal_10">507 KCAL</string>

</resources>